REZA **MALEK**

Las Vegas, NV · (949)667-8888 · rezmalek7@gmail.com

LinkedIn · Portfolio

I am a highly motivated and dependable Front End Developer with a stellar customer service record and superb work ethic. I specialize in JavaScript and have professional experience working with HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and React. I am a life-long learner and would like to have the opportunity to grow my skills while contributing to worthwhile projects.

EXPERIENCE

OCT 2017 - MAY 2020

FRONT END DEVELOPER, OnlineTickets.com

- Assisted colleagues in developing designs for company's website and converting them into interactive web elements.
- Maintained and updated HTML, CSS, and JavaScript templates on regular basis and as required.
- Used SEO best practices to elevate company's web presence; achieved top 10 Google rankings on several highly competitive keywords.

SEP 2015 - MAR 2020

PHOTOGRAPHER/WEB DEVELOPER, Livia Photo

- Produced compelling photographs for clients including real estate agencies, interior designers, and advertisers.
- Oversaw all aspects of business management including financial, marketing, and customer service
- Built responsive property websites for realtors to showcase their properties.

EDUCATION

FEB 2011 - JUL 2012

MBA IN COMMUNICATION, Limkokwing University

SEP 2005 - JUN 2009

BACHELOR OF ART IN PHOTOGRAPHY, Art & Architecture University

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Bootstrap, SCSS, React
- ECMAScript 6+

- Adobe Photoshop
- Communication
- Teamwork and Collaboration

CERTIFICATION

ServiceNow Certified System Administrator